留步 都不许走
Hold up! Nobody leave.
某人 我指的绝对不是麦克斯
Someone, and I'm not naming Max,
一直在偷餐厅的东西
has been stealing from the diner.
餐厅也一直从我身上偷东西啊
Well, the diner has been stealing from me.
我的青春 精力
Youth, energy,
生存意志
will to live.
新规定 任何员工离店前
So new policy: before any employee leaves,
需经过搜身检查
there will be a pat-down.
我多少年前就想推这条规定了
I tried to start that policy years ago.
说真的吗 阿憨
Seriously, Han?
你真想靠这种手段
Is that really how you want to get
来首次登"二垒"吗
to second base for the first time?
虽不理想 但吾亦无悔之
It's not ideal, no.
麦克斯 你先来
Max, you're first.
行
Fine.
你搜吧 机械战矮子
Feel me up, Low-bo-cop.
这是啥子
What's this?
那是奶子 悲催的孩子
It's a boob, sad man.
这个呢 是博洛尼亚腊肠
This, however, is bologna.
鄙视你 明天还得靠它假冒三文鱼呢
Shame on you! That's tomorrow's salmon.
在这个坦白的时刻
While we're coming clean,
我想说我三年前偷用了你的身份
I stole your identity three years ago.
现在一切摆平了 不过当时
It's over now, but I was caught up
我深陷类似《谍影重重》般的麻烦呢
in a kind of Jason Bourne situation.
卡洛琳 接下来我要搜你
Caroline, I'm coming to you next.
我本以为这身制服
And I thought this uniform
会是今日碰过我身子的最糟糕的东西呢
would be the worst thing touching my body today.
小提醒 我是人类 不是东西
Quick reminder: I'm a human being.
卡洛琳 当个不心急的妹"纸"好吗
Caroline, literally slow your roll.
知道人生会触菊花底
Well, if you're gonna hit bottom,
总是得先准备好擦菊花的道具嘛
you better have something to wipe it with.
厄尔
Earl--
我知道你绝对不会做
Now, I know you are not
指控一个黑人偷东西这种事
about to accuse a black man of stealing...
尤其在今时今日反歧视的政治气候下
in this current political climate.
当然不会啦
No, of course not.
我只是想祝你有个美好的夜晚
I was just going to wish you a wonderful evening.
给 麦克斯
Here, Max.
我这份腊肠你拿去吧
You can have my bologna.
我...
And I just--
我想我爱你
I think I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
卡洛琳
Uh, Caroline?
太好了
Oh, good.
你还带了人来目睹我这一幕
You brought someone else with you to see that.
欧文 卡洛琳 卡洛琳 欧文
Owen, Caroline. Caroline, Owen.
欧文 进我房去 卡洛琳 慢走不送
Owen, bedroom. Caroline, later.
欧文 幸会
Owen, nice to meet you.
听你的口音 是来自费城吗
Do I detect a Philadelphia accent?
我都还没说过话呢
I haven't said anything yet.
这酷炫牌生奶油被你搞到完全不酷了呢
But I gotta tell you, you really took the cool out of Cool Whip.
进本小姐香闺吧
Let's go in my room.
麦克斯 其实现在挺晚了
Oh, actually, Max, it's, uh--it's kinda late.
我明天还得早起上班
I gotta be at work early.
今晚跟你玩得很愉快 晚安啦
But I had a good time. Good night.
明天打给你 我们再约
I'll call you tomorrow. We'll do something.
额
Oh...
滴
my...
神
God.
天下第一惨事终于发生了
It finally happened.
有人不想跟我上床
Someone doesn't want to have sex with me!
他说他明天得早起上班
He said he gotta be at work early.
这不怪吗
Isn't that weird?
你居然跟有工作的人约会这事吗
That you're dating a guy with a job?
的确是怪到炸
Yeah, that is weird.
麦克斯 说不定你终于遇到
Max, maybe you finally met a guy
一个想先了解你
who wants to get to know you
再帮你宽衣解带的男人
before he jumps into bed with you.
或许他是你人生中那个真爱
Maybe Owen's the one.
"那个"不想跟我上床的人吗
The one that won't have sex with me!
所以当这一块
So what happens around here
没状况发生时 我们要干什么呢
when nothing happens around here?
当那种"状况"没有发生时
Well, when that's not happening,
吃起司蛋糕是不错选择
cheesecake is a fun alternative.
我从店里偷了一个蛋糕 因为我以为
I stole one from the diner 'cause I thought
你不会在家 我又会难过
you wouldn't be home and I'd be sad.
这蛋糕也是夹双腿间偷回来的吗
You hide that between your legs too?
开门
Open up!
我闻到有起司蛋糕
I smell cheesecake!
你们一定知道这味道代表啥
And you know what that smells like.
闺蜜谈心
Girl talk.
闺蜜谈心吗
Girl talk?
如果我们"拉拉"松神经 就不会染上"感情"了
All right, but if we lez out, nobody catch feelings.
我指的是聊些姑娘们的心事
Eh, I'm just talking about a little chick-ity chat.
朋友跟朋友之间分享心事
You know, friends sharing with friends
在一个安全放心的环境下聊
in a completely safe environment.
我最近梦到好多次...
Well, I've been having this recurring dream--
你下次还会再梦到
Yeah, well, you'll have it again.
来聊聊我的事吧
Let's talk about me.
姐妹们 奥列格跟我"做"个没完没了
Girls, Oleg and I have been having a lot of sex.
站着日 坐着顶
You know, standing up, sitting down,
电梯里操 电扶梯上干
on a elevator, on a escalator.
同时又上又下 上上下下
Going down and up at the same time.
所有都是无套中出 结果还是没怀上
All of that unprotected sex, and still no baby.
你丫敢情是来这里显摆的吗
Did you just come here to brag?
苏菲
You know, Sophie,
有时候当人们怀不上孩子
sometimes when people have trouble getting pregnant,
就会去找医生检查
they see a doctor.
苏菲 你都上哪去了
Sophie, where did you go?
被你按在性爱秋千的我一抬头 就发现你不见了
I looked up from the harness, and you were gone.
卡洛琳觉得我们中的一人
Well, Caroline thinks one of us...
她绝对没有明指某一人
And she's not pointing fingers at anyone,
但我们中的一人
but one of us...
可能需要去做一下精虫检测
you know, may need to get the sperm tested.
行行行 可是我出了名的射不准
All right, but I've been known to miss the cup.
厄尔
All right, Earl.
在昨晚的约会之后 我得来一发安慰炮
After last night's date, I need a rebound.
你可以把我介绍给你的朋友了
I'm ready for you to set me up with your friend.
迟了 他已经死了
He's dead.
我没说是哪个朋友啊
I didn't say which friend.
他们全死光了 麦克斯
They're all dead, Max.
我去 一个男的不跟你上床
Jeez, one guy doesn't want to sleep with you,
你就要开始小阴抓老鸡了吗
and you're sweatin' to the oldies?
花
Flowers?
天啊 不会是来给我上坟的吧
Oh, no! Am I dead too?
我来找麦克斯
I'm looking for Max.
她说她不在这里工作
She said she doesn't work here.
他来这里干嘛啊
What is he doing here?
这也太尴尬了吧
It's so awkward seeing a guy
跟昨晚没见到我裸体的约会对象见面
the day after he doesn't see you naked.
这花送你
These are for you.
花吗
Flowers?
如果还有下次 我先声明
For future reference, I'm more of a
我那种是喜爱麦芽酒的姑娘
"Mickey's Malt Liquor" Kind of girl.
我们能到那个卡座聊聊吗
Hey, can we talk over there in that booth?
那得看你的身体免疫系统多强了
It depends. How's your immune system?
卡洛琳 帮我照看一下我的区
Caroline, cover my tables.
我先把这些花放进餐厅的水中
First I'll put these in some diner water.
希望这些花喜欢水中漂浮的肉渣
I hope these flowers like little floating meat bits.
所以... 你带我共进晚餐
So...you take me to dinner,
待我如一名淑女
treat me like a lady,
还给我送花
and bring me flowers.
说吧 你是玩哪种变态玩意啊
What kind of sick stuff are you into?
麦克斯 我非常喜欢你
Max, I like you a lot.
那你怎么还不把我压在身下
Then why aren't you laying on top of me somewhere?
我想我们先多了解彼此再上床
Look, I want us to get to know each other before we have sex
这样我们才能更信任彼此
to be able to trust each other,
更能保守彼此的秘密
keep each other's secrets.
好吧 告诉我你的安全词 就开干吧
Fine; just tell me your safe word, and let's go.
我的安全词是"锅贴"
Mine is "Pot sticker."
我是认真的
I'm serious,
因为当我们真做爱时 你会发现
'cause when we do have sex, you're gonna find out
我那个...
that I'm not...
我的下面异于常人
well, I'm not regular down there.
"异于常人"吗
Um..."not regular"?
所以是看起来像...
So does it look something like...
这样吗
This?
不是 而且比这个大
No. And bigger.
所以是类似...
Uh, so something like...
这样吗
This?
不是 它没有长脸
No, it doesn't have a face.
麦克斯 厨房里出问题了
Max, something's wrong in the kitchen.
不是这里 这里没有任何问题
Not here. Nothing's wrong here.
跟我来就是了
Just come with me.
明天能跟你见面吗
Uh, well, can I see you tomorrow?
当然啊 但你至少得迟到一下
Sure, but at least be late.
我才能有些空间借题发挥
Give me something to work with.
我听到他说的话了
I heard what he said.
"下面异于常人"是什么鬼啊
What the heck does "not regular down there" mean?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只知道他说的不是
All I know is, it doesn't mean...
这样
this.
一切皆有可能
It could be anything.
我曾经在莫斯科看过千奇百怪的鸡鸡特展
In Moscow, I saw this amazing penis freak show,
"俄版的信不信由你"博物馆
"Ripleyvitch Believe It or Nyet."
看完之后 久久不能忘"鸡"
I'm not over it "nyet."
你真的还要再跟他约会吗
So you're really gonna go out with Owen again?
你这样是在玩"屌"罗斯轮盘啊 少女
I mean, you're playing penis roulette down there.
毒鸟猛鸡 鸡飞鸟跳
It could be gnarly or wonky or...
甚至猛鬼吹鸡
truly haunting.
太有道理
You're right.
这"鸡"我必须得看啊
I gotta see it!
好了 再跟我说一遍
Okay, tell me again.
像跟十岁小孩那样说话
Talk to my like I'm a 10-year-old...
一个十岁大奶少女
with overdeveloped boobs.
很简单
It's simple.
欧文想要先了解你
Owen just wants to get to know you
再跟你滚床单
before he has sex with you.
他也太变态了 人家才十岁
That is sick! I'm ten.
来 我们来练习一遍
Here. Let's practice.
假装我是欧文 问我问题
Pretend I'm Owen, and ask me something.
欧文 什么时候要扒下小裤裤啊
So, Owen, when you gonna take "dem" pants off?
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
你们觉得会有人注意到
Do you think anyone would notice
你们明天关店
if you closed your shop
因为我们要去过一个闺蜜之日吗
and we had a girls' day tomorrow?
苏菲 我们明天要去哪里
Where we going tomorrow, Sophie?
拜托是附近康尼岛玩
Say Coney Island, say Coney Island.
我们要去看妇科医生
We're going to a gynecologist!
奥列格说他会去找医生检查精虫
Yeah, see, Oleg said that he'd get himself checked out,
为了表现团队精神
so, to be a team player,
我也打算去让医生检查我"前院的水井"
I'm gonna let a doctor poke around my front bottom.
我感到无上光荣
Well, obviously I'm honored,
但我必须得回答"打死都不去"
but that's gonna be a hard "no" from me.
姑娘们
Oh, girls!
我不想自己去
I don't want to go alone.
我好害怕
I'm scared!
在波兰 我们的医生也是镇上的屠夫
You know, in Poland, our doctor was also the butcher,
因为他已经有白色屠宰袍
you know, because he already had the white coat
外加钢铁放血台了
and the metal draining table.
想象一下 跟一群紧张不安的羊
I mean, you try sharing a waiting room
同处在等候室
with a bunch of nervous sheep.
咩
Baaah!
Baaaah!
羊咩咩的往事回忆吗
Sheep flashbacks?
那我必须得去看看啊
I am obviously in.
到时见
Buh-bye.
现在来到羊
This is the part where the sheep
真正开始害怕的部分了
really started to freak out.
咩
Baaah!
苏菲 别紧张
Sophie, just relax,
要不换上这件纸长袍
and maybe change into this paper gown
好让医生检查"水井"时能更方便点
so the doctor can have better access.
虽然我说这种话
And as I'm saying this,
但我真不知道我来干嘛
I really wonder what I am doing here.
我不需要长袍
Well, I don't need a gown.
我已经把我塑身裤从中间撕开了
I ripped the middle right out of my Spanx.
是欧文
It's Owen.
"今晚一起吃饭怎么样
"How about dinner tonight?
意大利菜 寿司 你想吃啥都行"
Italian, sushi, whatever you're in the mood for."
我想来点...[摇床声]
I'm in the mood for a little...
麦克斯 你何不把他邀家里
Max, why don't you invite him over?
你可以给他做一顿浪漫晚餐
You can make him a romantic dinner,
然后你还能看
and then you can watch
《美国恐怖故事:惊恐之"鸟"》
"American Horror Story: Penis Edition."
科臣斯基小姐 我是瑟顿医生
Miss Kuchenski, I'm Dr. Surden.
咩
Baaah!
科臣斯基小姐 你怎么不把长袍穿上
Miss Kuchenski, why aren't you wearing a gown,
为什么你要把双膝并拢
and why are you clenching your knees?
天啊
Oh, no.
我居然从小六变成小文了
I got the lock legs.
等等 我有个主意
Hang on; I got an idea.
好痒哦
That tickles!
快出招 医生
Make your move now, Doc!
好痒
That tickles!
咩
Baaah!
要不我让护士
Uh, m-m-maybe I'll have the nurse
拿点东西来安抚你的情绪
bring something to relax you.
如果可以点东西 我要来杯水
I'll take a water if we're getting stuff.
我得离开这里
I got to get out of here.
可是苏菲 他还没给你做检查呢
But, Sophie, he hasn't even examined you yet.
到底怎么回事
What's going on?
你今天比平时怪...一百倍
You're acting odd-er than usual.
万一我和奥列格不能生孩子
Well, what if Oleg and I can't have a baby
是因为问题出在我身上
because there's something wrong with me?
我是说 万一奥列格的小蝌蚪没问题
I mean, what if it's not Oleg's swimmers?
是我这片池塘有毛病呢
What if it's my pool?
那岂不是很...
I mean, that would be so...
可悲...咩
sad.
我希望事情会是如此展开
Here's how I want things to unfold.
你觉得他那件"事"还能展开吗
Do you think his thing will unfold?
就像喜剧鬼片那样神展开
Like Beetlejuice?
你觉得你能做到真的去了解他吗
Do you think you can handle getting to know him?
我被你弄得好心烦啊
I'm getting really upset.
我问题都准备好了
Hey, I have questions prepared.
没事的
I'll be fine.
你才是那个接下来
You're the one who has to sit at Starbucks
要在星巴克坐三个小时 听流浪汉巴布
and listen to homeless Barb pitch her screenplay
推销她的烂剧本的人
for the next three hours.
讲话注意点
Uh, careful.
麦克斯 你的"货"到了
Max, your package is here.
希望你喜欢白葡萄酒
Hope you like white wine.
当然 我可是跟白妞住一起
Of course. I live with her.
那"妞"要走了
And "her" Is leaving.
很高兴见到你 欧文
Nice to see you, Owen.
祝你俩用餐愉快 好好了解彼此哦
You two have a great time getting to know each other.
别让这家伙烦死你
Don't let this one talk your ear off.
她可是话超多的那种姑娘
She's the type of girl that just loves to talk.
你今晚真漂亮
You look beautiful.
还不怕麻烦亲自下厨
You went to all this trouble.
是的 谢谢夸奖
I did. Thank you.
你看起来...
And you look...
"爷"漂亮
man-beautiful.
我们要不要坐下 开始了解对方呢
Shall we sit and get to know each other?
比如
Like, for instance,
"你妻子的同事盖里
"Your wife's work friend Gary
邀请她一起出差
invites her away on a business trip
他们俩同住一间房
where they'd be sharing one room.
你会 A"
Do you, A--"
-麦克斯 -我知道
- Max. - I know.
一看就知她跟他一腿
Obviously, she bones him.
我说的"了解对方"
When I said "get to know each other,"
不是要跟你玩"顾忌"这种选择游戏
I wasn't thinking "Scruples."
我更像是会玩"饥饿河马"那种游戏的人
I'm more of a "Hungry Hungry Hippos" guy.
我希望我能买得起正版的"顾忌"
I wish I could afford "Scruples."
这是盗版货"咕鸡"
This is "Scrumples."
听着 我不知道该怎么做
Look, I don't know how to do this.
我觉得好蠢
I feel stupid.
你可能觉得自己蠢
You may feel stupid,
但你现在看起来好可爱
but you look really cute right now.
真的吗
I do?
有多可爱
How cute do I look?
A 超级无敌可爱
A, super very a lot.
B
B--
我选A
Oh, it's A.
说真的 你从来没试着了解过别人吗
Seriously, have you never gotten to know anybody ever?
我...不知道
I...don't know.
人们都是怎么了解对方
How do people get to know each other?
我是指 你想了解我什么啊
I mean, what do you want to know?
我小时候家里没什么钱
We didn't have any money growing up.
我妈妈是一名酒鬼
My mom was an alcoholic.
我爸爸...
My father was...
连《寻父记》的栏目组都找不到他在哪儿
not able to be located by Maury Povich.
我们经常搬家
We moved a lot because
因为我们房车的刹车不管用
the parking brake on our house didn't work.
现在你了解我了吧
So now you know me.
我猜你也要走了
I guess you'll be leaving.
这是不是 A 告别吻
Was that an A, kiss good-bye?
那是因为你很可爱 还跟我分享你的事
That's for being cute and for sharing that.
我真的认为我们该跳过晚餐
I definitely think we should skip dinner--
把蜡烛吹灭 因为我担心着火
blow this out 'cause I worry about fire;
我个人对火有阴影
that's something about me--
我们直接进入"甜点"吧
and go straight to dessert.
我现在想聊了 会不会很欠揍啊
Is it weird that I want to talk now?
哇 直奔主题啊
Oh, wow. Going right for it, huh?
这老娘想破脑袋也画不出来
Never would've drawn that.
真不敢相信你居然不告诉我
I can't believe you won't tell me
欧文"下面"有什么异于常人之处
what's not regular about Owen's "down there."
我什么都告诉你
I tell you everything.
行
Fine.
在第一个卷心菜沙拉桶那等我
Meet me at the first coleslaw tub.
自己来
Come alone.
-出去 -但我在做饭呢
- Get out. - But I'm cooking.
出去
Get out.
好吧 反正做出来也是垃圾
Fine. This is garbage anyway.
行啦行啦 告诉我吧
Okay, okay. Tell me.
好吧
All right.
记得在《欢乐满屋》里
Remember on "Full House,"
当你以为只有一个米雪儿
when you thought there was one Michelle,
但其实是有两个米雪儿
but there were actually two Michelles...
你干嘛提起
Why are you bringing up
我这辈子最疯狂的那段日子
one of the craziest days of my life?
他有俩
He has two.
俩什么
Two what?
欧文有两根鸡鸡
Owen has two penises!
为什么这么难理解呢
Why is it so hard to understand?
真的能有这种事吗
Is that a thing that can happen?
有啊 这叫双阴茎畸形
Yes. It's called diphallia.
我刚在网上搜了一下
I just Googled it.
这是一种医学症状
It's a medical condition in which a male
一个男人天生有两根鸡鸡
is born with two penises.
有两屌 错不了？
The only case in which two dongs make a right.
奥列格 这本该是我们的私密谈话
Oleg, this was supposed to be private.
你的意思是"私处"谈话吧
I think you mean "privates."
球数[蛋数]是多少
What's the ball count?
奥列格 别搜了
Oleg, stop Googling!
我没有搜
I'm not Googling.
我现在跟苏菲打电话呢
Now I'm on the phone with Sophie.
谁有两根鸡鸡呀
Who has two penises?
麦克斯的男朋友
Max's boyfriend.
你们在里面干嘛呢
What's going on back here?
麦克斯的男朋友有两根鸡鸡
Max's boyfriend has two penises!
好啦 真是够了
Okay! Okay! That's it.
不许再谈论欧文的鸡鸡
No more talk about Owen's penis
或他的二号鸡
or his other penis.
麦克斯 他不是你要找的那"一"个人
Well, Max, I guess he's not the one...
他是"对"的人
'cause he's the two.
其实我还挺喜欢他的
Actually, I really like him,
绝不是因为我可以跟他另一根鸡鸡出轨
and not just because I can cheat on him with him.
麦克斯 你在开玩笑吧
Max, you can't be serious.
我们每个人都会有自己的问题
Hey, everyone has something wrong with them.
我的内心支离破碎
I'm messed up on the inside.
至少欧文的问题就在外面 你可以看得见
At least Owen's is right out there where you can see it.
欧文刚特意过来跟我聊两句
Owen's stopping by just to chat.
我现在喜欢聊天了
I like talking now.
我想我会告诉他
I think I'm gonna tell him
我第一次离家出走的事
about the first time I ran away from home.
我爬到了底特律
I crawled to Detroit.
麦克斯 我觉得这样很棒
Max, I think it's great you were able
你能忽视欧文的症状
to look past Owen's situation.
即使只看其中一根 也会觉得很恶心吧
Even the sight of one of them can be disturbing.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
好消息
Oh, good news.
奥列格的精子龙精虎猛
Oleg's got strong sperm.
这块饼干我也吃不下了
Well, that's the end of this cookie.
坏消息是...
And the bad news is...
我以为刚才那就是坏消息
Oh, I thought that was the bad news.
我回去看医生 他说
I went back to the doctor, and he said
我还能怀孕
I can still get pregnant.
只是会比较耗时费工
It's just gonna take a while, you know,
因为我的蛋[卵子]有点像这餐厅的蛋
'cause my eggs are a bit like the eggs here at the diner.
虽然严格来说没有坏
You know, not exactly bad,
但也将近过期了
just real close to the use-by date.
苏菲 什么让你改变心意回去看医生
Sophie, what made you go back to the doctor?
我经常进行深刻的自我反省
Well, you know, I was doing a lot of soul-searching,
还有我的钱包落在那里了
and I left my purse there.
于是我就想 既然我都在这了
So I figured, you know, while I'm here,
何不做个检查
why not take a look, you know?
就像麦克斯所说
I mean, like Max said,
每个人都会有些问题
everybody's got something.
不是我瞎吹
Well, not to brag,
但我那位有两个"问题"
but mine's got two somethings.
你好 我来找...
Hi. I'm here for, uh...
"两"人桌 我是说一人
Table for two. I mean one!
我为什么要用"两"呢
Why did I say two?
我不知道 祝你今天愉快
I don't know. Have a good one.
你俩也是 我是说你也是
You too. I mean, one!
你好呀
Oh, hi. Yeah.
我听说了很多你的事
I've heard a lot about you.
但也不是一切啦
You know, but not everything.
就"两"件事而已
You know, just a couple of things.
-她知道了吗 -什么
- She knows? - What?
不
Um, no.
这就像跟偶像猫王见面
This is like meeting Elvis
前提是他有两根鸡鸡 还没死在马桶上
if Elvis had two penises and didn't die on his toilet.
好吧 他们都知道了
Okay. They all know.
欧文 等等 对不起嘛
Owen, wait! Wait. I'm sorry.
我以为他走路姿态会不一样呢
Uh, I expected him to walk differently.
其他人也这么认为吗
Did anybody else think that?
是啊 我在想他是不是三角裤和四角裤一起穿
Yeah, I was wondering if he wears briefs and boxers.
他会不会让我跟他的"无间双龙"自拍呢
I was wondering if he'd let me take a selfie with them.
各位 麦克斯真的很喜欢欧文
Guys, Max really likes Owen,
现在这感情可能得告"吹"了
and she might have blown it.
不得不说 "吹"起来是双倍的活儿啊
Which, again, seems like a lot of work.
怎么样了
What happened?
他跟我分手了
He broke up with me.
他居然跟你分手
He broke up with you?
他说我背叛了他的信任
He said I betrayed his trust,
我说 不管我想不想
and I said, whether I like it or not,
你们都知道了
you guys know everything.
你们是我沉重的负担
You're part of the package.
那他怎么说
And what did he say?
他说我的负担对他来说太重了
He said my package was too much for him.
他好意思说你负担太重[鸡鸡太多]
Your package is too much?
他自己可是"双龙"出海
I mean, he's driving a double-decker.
卷心菜沙拉桶 自己来
Coleslaw tub. Come alone.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
I'm fine.
我不是很信你
I don't really believe you,
但我知道有东西能让你好过点
but I do know something that might make you feel better.
天啊 不要吧
Oh, God! No!
闺蜜谈心靠边闪
No more girl talk.
私人珍藏
Private stash.
我在这里经常觉得难过
I get sad a lot in here.
我真的很喜欢他
I really liked him.
我按你说的做了
I did what you said,
我让他了解我的内心
and I let him get to know me.
我再也不会这样做了
I'm never doing that again.
这样感觉不够力啊
This isn't doing it for me.
我会想死他的
I'm gonna miss him.